Be very cautious when it comes to committing to uptime numbers.
如果要落实更新号 请非常谨慎
Do the math and make sure that you can reasonably achieve the numbers being asked for.
执行数学 并确保您可以合理地实现所要求的数字
Allow downtime will be the number of minutes that
允许停机时间将是
you are allowed to be down without violating your SLA.
您可以在不违反 SLA的情况下关闭
Allow downtime is typically measured on a monthly basis.
允许停机时间通常按月测量
Since different months have different lengths,
因为不同的月份有不同的长度
SLAs often use a 30-day measurement to calculate downtime,
SLA 经常使用 30 天的测量来计算停机时间
even for months that have a different number of days.
甚至几个月的时间也不一样
Let's get out the calculator and do some math.
让我们拿出计算器 做一些数学运算
How much downtime would a 99 percent SLA allow for?
99% SLA 允许多少停机时间 ?